[ED]
[Applause]
I'll come back when I'm done with makeup!
Wow!
It's an extra channel! Oh, you're going to be on the Extra Channel?
The Omake Channel!
I want each person to speak at least once.
Pappa-pappa-pappa-pappa-pappa!
Pappa-pappa-pappa-pappa
Chuksi-shun!
Oh no!
I'm off to Okara-oshi.
Because it's a little dirty.
It's an extra channel!
Oh, but it's not finished yet.
Well, I'm surprisingly an earring person,
I'm the only one of the senior members who doesn't have open ears,
It's hard to find such a cute pair of earrings like these, isn't it?
Jingling!
Oh, wait. Saoriko can do the Soroban, can't she?
Saori's specialty is Soroban.
Can you do it?
Please do. Well, please calculate the amount of Saori's allowance for me.
Thousands of yen? Tens of thousands of yen?
100 yen.
I only get 100 yen.
It's just a handout.
Oh, I have nothing else to say.
I want each of you to speak at least once.
Eat a lot...talk...I said eat.
All I have is an appetite...that's it.
I am Yagishii of Tsubaki Factory.
I always watch the extra channel 3.
Freely? What should I do? Let's talk together.
Mr. Tanimoto, I heard that your face is not finished yet.
But it's totally fine.
It's totally fine.
Oh, she's probably prettier than I am.
What are you talking about?
She's cute even though she's not finished yet.
I have a small face right now, so I'm a little behind...
Please stop it. My face is a little swollen today.
Really? Seriously?
And I ate a bag of chips yesterday.
Kansai de-soy sauce.
That's right. I got a bag of soy sauce from Kansai.
So I ate a bag of chips on the bullet train.
After the party, I was alone.
I shared one with Mr. Asakura and the manager.
I ate all the rest by myself.
My face is swollen.
That's why my face is swollen,
Marin Fukuda and Runo-chan have arrived.
I'd like to take over here.
Yes, I will. Then, here come Marin Fukuda and Runo Yofu.
Yes!
Nice to meet you, Mare-chan!
Bye bye bye!
This time
Omake Channel
In this video
I'll be in this video for the longest time
I'm going to talk a lot
I will talk a lot.
baboon
I just finished rehearsal and it's during the first performance.
I've had my make-up done and it's now finished.
How do you like my hair and makeup today?
It's the anniversary of rock 'n' roll!
Everyone says they want to go to Tsubaki House to rock the house.
I'm going to rock dance!
Yay! Bye bye!
Are you spinning this?
One for each of us.
Is it spinning?
It's spinning.
Let's see...
Today is...
It's our 6th anniversary live.
Look at this.
It's our sixth anniversary.It's our sixth anniversary.
So, I made it a little bit stronger.
I tried to make it a little stronger.
We are going to perform with a live band,
Some of them I have worked with before in acoustic live, and some for the first time,
I was so happy to see so many people working for Tsubaki.
I am happy that so many people have worked for Tsubaki.
I want to make everyone feel happy about the concert,
I want to make the people who came to the show feel that it was a lot of fun,
I want to do my best so that everyone who comes to the show will think it was a lot of fun.
But most of all, I want to enjoy myself!
Here is an extra channel!
Please check it out!
You look like Shichigo-san!
Yay!
This time, it's a dango!
We'll be back in about 5 minutes.
Shul is here!
I want to make the most appearances in this video!
The longest.
So be careful not to get cut.
Oh, no!
I'm off!
But they won't cut it unless something really bad happens, right?
What?
I'm wearing an enamel jacket.
I put it on.
What do you think?
Do you think it looks cool?
Shine, shine, shine.
What am I going to say?
I have no idea.
Please look at me as I am today. Is it time already?
Okay, I'm off.
I'm off.
I heard that the show is about to start.
We always do a guineprop investment before the show starts,
I didn't do it this time. I didn't do it this time.
So I'm not sure if I'll be able to handle it,
But I'm sure I'll be excited about the show,
I'll do my best and let that tension carry me through.
I'm going to go. I'm going to have fun.
I'm going to go.
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best. I'm off.
The show is about to begin.
Heart.
I'm off.
just finished
Freshly done.
Oh, is this turning? Just now.
Oh, is it spinning?
Wrecks are spinning?
The first one is done!
What I want to do in the extra channel. A woman who prioritizes what she wants to do in the extra channel after the show.
What I prepared for today. I had a lot of throat lozenges of various kinds in my cover, but I didn't lick them,
Well, I didn't lick them.
I finished after one performance!
Thank you very much!
It was fun!
It went by so fast!
I did it with a hook.
I'm home!
I'm back! It was fun!
Only one more show to go!
I enjoyed one more show!
There are 10 more shows!
Just one more!
The best with everyone!
Only one!
She's the cutest!
Yes!
Extra channel!
Let's start!
End!
What's the end?
That's the last of the extras you're gonna ride here, right?
Ready!
Yeah!Hey!
How much did you look like?
Don't look like a middle croaker.
Ready!
Ya!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Pan!
Ah! It's spinning!
All the way around!
Hello!
Let's see, now...
I'm between the first and second show.
Well, the lunches are
It was so delicious!
I ate all of them!
Yes!
He looked a little sad.
They've been turning this place for a long time.
I'm looking forward to it!
I'll do my best!
It's an extra bonus!
Ugh! I missed it!
Oh, man!
You'll have to repeat that!
Okay, here's how we're going to do it.
Oh, I see, I see.
Oh, so that's how it's done.
Okay! Please do it!
Well, I'll be on the extra channel.
What do you want to do?
Yes!
Why, um...
I've been on the show a lot.
I wasn't the one who got the silver shield.
Ah!
Oh, you wonder?
Hmm.
I see. Then let's go for gold next time.
A million.
What? What? What's out there?
The prize money.
We're going for a million.
Have you subscribed to our channel yet?
No, I haven't.
What?
You have to subscribe!
Don't watch it!
It's too much!
You must subscribe!
Oh, wait! Please don't do the slide thing because I don't like these two.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, don't do the 15, 20 second thing!
Please don't do that.
And us.
Watch us.
It's good to look at us, right?
It's good to look.
If you all look at them.
You'll get a good thing.
Ha-ha-ha.
LOL.
Hey, hey.
Okay, okay.
Bye-bye.
Extra Channel
Start!
End.
I'm here, right? I have to put a button on it.
If I do it like this, it'll just come off.
So I have a button here.
Now I'm going to stop it in front of you.
Here? Here?
Here?
I'm not sure.
There it is.
Is it okay if it's a little bit plain? It's good, right?
Oh! Something I want to do on the extra channel!
Yeah! We have a lot of things!
Well, what do you want to do?Well, what do you want to do?
First, baked rice cooking.
No, but we're doing it at Happisugo.
I'd like to do it with the Omake Channel, across group boundaries!
Ah! Nigene-san! You've come to the right place!
Ah!
Please don't run away.
You're in the picture more than I am.
What? Oh, no! Get out of the picture.
Don't take any more pictures.
I'll always be in the picture.
What? Oh, my God!
Because I want to be in the picture for the longest time this time.
We're in the picture the longest.
I shouldn't have called Mr. Garlic.
Here, I and Kino are getting more and more time.
It's getting longer and longer!
Let's count the number of times I'm in the picture.
How much time am I in the picture?
And Mr. Niinuma and Mr. Akiyama?
Hmmm...
What? Already?
When are we meeting? Soon?
Okay, bye-bye!
Bye!
What? Ready!
I'm off!
Chekila!
He said he did it every time!
It's open!
First one in!
Yay! Second on the line!
Yeah!
Let's go!
That's a good one!
I can use that!
Get out of the way!
Yes!
Yeah!
Good traveling!
Yeah! Good job, guys!
Ha!
Heart!
See you soon!
Bring memories!
See you again!
Luno's minions!
Luno!
Yeah!
Oh, man! He's boggled!
We gotta get to this bridge!
We gotta get out of here!
What? This is great!
We can go to the Lune. We can go under the Lune.
Sayonara.
Does it work?
And I just banged it into the microphone.
Maybe now, for those of you watching.
I'm going to break the chair for the longest time!
I'm borrowing a chair.
Why? When Mr. Shinnuma came in, a rival for the longest record appeared.
Setiate will be cut too.
So I just have to do my best not to be cut?
Oh no, it's difficult.
It's difficult.
There is a limit to the length of the film.
Oh, that's terrible.
What should I do? How long do I borrow a chair? How long do I borrow a chair until I'm called?
The point of today's outfit is this.
I like the lace.
Many other people don't wear much under their T-shirts,
I think it stands out because I'm wearing lace.
And then there's my hair, although it's clean,And then there's the hair, although it's neat,
I wanted to put it down, so I put it down full of ears and straightened it down.
I had the pins made sparkling.
There was one more outfit, the Mesabelle jacket,
Isn't that really cool? It's so shiny and cool.
If you rewind it, you can see it,
I don't know. Maybe you can go ahead and watch it.
Let's see...enthusiasm. I know it's over, but I'll say my enthusiasm.
I'm working hard to make this video the longest on the channel.
I'm Shiyumi Nagisaki.
I'm taking selfies all the time by myself.
I'm talking on camera.
What was fun at first,
At first, Masayume's, you know,
Oh, no. I'm in too many pictures.
The first part is the opening curtain.
Yes, that's right. That was fun, wasn't it?
It says, "Feel free to talk, and you are welcome to talk as much as you want.
Don't aim for the longest performance.
Then you should aim for the longest appearance, too.
That's not what I meant.
You can use your speech more than you think.
You're only talking to yourself.
Because everyone who talks seems to be busy.
I thought you were talking to someone else.
But I'm not,
I'm trying my best.
And if I'm in the picture with everyone else, I'll have more rivals.
You have a loud voice, don't you?
It's easier for the microphone to hear a loud voice.
You know, for musicals.
I was in the hallway as if I was in a play.
I think it's great that today's performance echoed through the hallway.
Good luck. I'll be rooting for you.
But, you know, lately, I haven't been able to do vocal practice because I'm not in the drama club.
I think my voice has gotten too quiet,
Please do your best.
I will continue to work hard so that I can make my voice louder.
What should I do? I'll talk some more.
Bye bye. Bye bye.